Susan Due Pearcy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Susan Due Pearcy collection, circa 1960-2014 1967
AFC 2014/028
Pearcy, Susan Due
approximately 5155 items
10 containers
8.5 linear feet
7 boxes
92 photographic prints: black-and-white and color; various sizes
1 negative: black-and-white; 35 mm
approximately 43 negatives (in 22 strips): color; 35 mm
approximately 22 negatives (in 22 strips): color; 120 format
7 transparencies: film, color; 35 mm
approximately 155 posters and drawings: linocuts, woodcuts, oil drawings, water drawings, sketches; various sizes
1 optical disc (DVD-R, 11 video files): optical, sound, color; 4 3/4 in.
19 pins, buttons, ribbon
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of original visual art, manuscripts, ephemera such as posters and newsletters, photographs and artifacts such as political buttons, which documents the United Farm Workers labor movement in California during the 1970s and the Civil Rights movement in southwest Georgia during the 1960s.
Provenance
Susan Due Pearcy; 2014
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Susan Due Pearcy collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
Susan Due Pearcy is an artist and the owner of Sugarloaf Studio in Barnesville, Maryland. Born in May 6, 1945, in St. Louis, Missouri, Susan studied art education at Southeast Missouri State University before earning a Bachelor of Science in painting, graphics and sculpture from New York University. She has worked at the Graphics Workshop and the Printmaker's Workshop in Maryland and her art has been displayed over 200 times both regionally and internationally including Russia, France and Argentina. She has been the recipient of many awards and recognitions. In 2009, she was selected as one of Maryland's Top 100 Women and is the Signature member of the Maryland Pastel Society.
In 1967, acting upon an invitation by Rev. Charles Sherrod, Susan, and her late husband Glen Pearcy, traveled to Georgia where they worked on the Southwest Georgia Project Newsletter. Glen wrote occasionally for the newsletter while Susan provided photos and sketches for the paper. In 1972, Richard Cook, a volunteer from the United Farm Workers (UFW) Union, beckoned to the couple to come to California. Susan and Glen moved from Georgia to work with the United Farm Workers at the central headquarters in La Paz, California, where Susan became the staff graphic artist for El Macriado. She designed woodblocks and linocut prints and created drawings for use on buttons, bumper strips, and in the newspaper. Susan also created the eagle that was used in the UFW's flag.
Scope and Content
The collection contains the original drawings and artwork Susan Due Pearcy created for the Southwest Georgia Project and the UFW Union including the original linocuts. It also includes a few copies of the original EL Macriado. The collection also includes some of Susan's orginal sketchbooks and artwork.
Arrangement
The Susan Due Pearcy collection (AFC 2014/028) is organized in five series:
Series 1: Southwest Georgia Project, 1967-2011
Series 2: United Farm Workers materials (UFW), 1970s-2014
Series 3: Glen Pearcy materials, 1966-2009
Series 4: Publications, 1972-1982
Series 5: Original artwork, 1967-undated
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Pearcy, Susan Due, creator, collector, donor.
Organizations
Southwest Georgia Project.; United Farm Workers.
Subjects
Civil rights movements--Georgia.; Labor movement--California.; Protest movements--United States--Pictorial works.
Form/Genre
Documentary photography.; Manuscripts.; Photographs.
Container List
- Series 1: Southwest Georgia Project (SWGP), 1967-2011
  - Dr. Clennon King et. al., undated, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/1)
    Includes newsletters, handwritten prayers, and a typed letter to Glen Pearcy from Dr. Clemmons King.
  - Mr. Willie Hall, 1967-1968, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/2)
    Includes logs from Grady County art class along with newspapers.
  - Manuscript materials supporting the SWGP (1/2), 1967-2011, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/3)
    Includes a report of the History of the Black man, children's drawings, newspaper showcasing children's drawings in the aftermath of MLK's murder, letter boycotting the MLK service at the city's auditorium in Albany, a financial report, a teaching plan by Susan Pearcy and a booklet of poems. See Box 6 Folder 3 for the New York Time Magazine paper of children's drawings.
  - Manuscript materials supporting the SWGP (1/2), 1967-2011, manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/3)
    New York Time Magazine with children's drawings.
    Separated from Box 1 Folder 3.
  - Manuscript materials supporting the SWGP (2/2), 1967-2011, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/4)
    Includes color prints of the Southwest Georgia Project reunion, a brochure Journey Down to the Path to Freedom, a report Significant Dates On Black Land Loss & Land Acquisition, and a RSVP list.
  - Southwest Georgia Project Reunion (1/2), 2000-2009, undated, 27 4 x 6 in. color prints (Box-folder 1/5)
    Prints documenting the reunion of the Southwest Georgia Project Reunion activists along with manuscript materials and a copy of The Albany Herald, June 5, 2009.
  - Southwest Georgia Project Reunion (2/2), 2000, 26 color prints (Box-folder 1/6)
    Prints documenting the reunion of the Southwest Georgia Project Reunion activists.
  - Poems and notes by Susan Pearcy, 1967, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/7)
    Handwritten and typed compositions by Susan Pearcy.
  - Programs, Southwest Georgia Project, 2000-2008, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/8)
    Includes flyers and brochures pertaining to the Southwest Georgia Project along with other African American civil justices including a newsletter, Captive Lives which highlights blacks in the penal system.
  - SCLS, Citizen Education Program, August 11, 1967, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Drawings 1967-undated, 30 ink and water drawings (Box-folder 1/10)
    Original ink and watercolor drawings and sketches of various subjects by Susan Pearcy.
  - Mockups for publication, undated, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/11)
    Photocopies of four images. One of the images was photographed by Joe Pfister and submitted by Glen Pearcy et. al. for a program in photography. Another was used on the cover of Southern Exposure: good times and growing pains, (5)1.
  - Newsletters (SWGP), 1966-2009, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/12)
    Includes newsletters from the Southwest Georgia Project.
  - Notes and interviews about education, 1967-1968, manuscript materials (Box-folder 1/13)
    Includes handwritten notes from an ASCS meeting, handwritten correspondence, paper of de-centralization, interviews about schools, personal biographical history, and newspaper clippings.
  - Greeting cards designed by S. Pearcy, 1960s, 5 greeting cards of various sizes (Box-folder 1/14)
    Cards designed by Susan for the Harambee shop ran by the Southwest Georgia Project.
  - Shirley Sherrod by Bob Sullivan, July 1988, 11 3 x 5 in. color prints; 10 120 color negative strips (Box-folder 1/15)
    Images by Bob Sullivan documenting the Southwest Georgia Project reunion.
  - Shirley Sherrod by Bob Sullivan, July 1988, AFC 2014/028: PH01-01; 10 color negative strips; 19 images (Box 5)
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Bob Sullivan, July 1988, 12 3 x 5 in. prints; 6 120 color negative strips (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Bob Sullivan, July 1988, AFC 2014/028: PH01-02; 6 color negative strips; 12 images (Box 5)
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Bob Sullivan, July 1988, 12 3 x 5 in. prints; 6 120 color negative strips (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Bob Sullivan, July 1988, AFC 2014/028: PH01-03; 6 color negative strips; 12 images (Box 5)
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Reunion, June 5-7, 2009, afc 2014028_dc01; 1 DVD-R (Box-folder 1/17)
    See afc2014028_dc01_aip
  - Southwest Georgia Project, Reunion, June 5-7, 2009, afc2014028_dc01_aip; 11 vob, ifo, bup video files, digital, sound, color
    Recording produced by Glean Pearcy Productions. Digital copy of DVD extracted from original by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes.
  - Georgia, undated, AFC 2014/028: PH01-04; 1 35mm black-and-white negative (Box-folder 1/18)
    Image of an individual walking by a flights of stairs.
  - Georgia, 1960s, AFC 2014/028: PH01-05; 1 35mm color slide (Box-folder 1/19)
    Image of two little girls.
  - Georgia, 1960s, AFC 2014/028: PH01-06; 1 35mm black-and-white slide (Box-folder 1/19)
    Image of an individual in an office.
  - SWGP line drawings, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR17-32, 46; 17 ink line drawings various sizes (Box-folder 9/1)
  - SWGP images, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR47-50, 126; 5 drawings (Box-folder 9/2)
    Includes 1 linocut of a man, 1 ink drawing: Mrs. Daniel and T, Block House, 11-18-71; 1 ink drawing of a man and another on the verso; 1 drawing of a woman; 1 black-and-white print pasted on a matte backing: Craft Class. Drawings by Susan Pearcy.
  - SWGP sketchbooks, 1960, 2 9 x 12 in. sketchbooks (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Susan's SWGP scrapbook, 1967-1968, 1 scrapbook; 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 1/21)
    Contains newspaper clippings, handwritten and typed letters including correspondence between Susan and her sister while Susan was living in Baker County, Georgia, 1967-1968.
- Series 2: United Farm Workers (UFW) materials, 1970s-2014
  This series is a mixture of manuscript materials, artwork and posters. Please note that the titles for the posters were taken directly from the items themselves. In regards to the artwork the titles which appear in italics were supplied by the artist. All other titles were supplied by the archivist.
  - Sketchbook, 1972-1978, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 2/1)
    Black hardcover sketchbook of different animals, landscape and individuals.
  - Harambee child development, 1972, manuscript materials (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Diana Lyons, correspondence, 1973-1974, manuscript materials; 5 color prints (Box-folder 2/3)
    Letter sent to Susan, from the Florida Boycott Director, about the victory of gaining better wages for the oranges and the potential need for posters.
  - Articles, 1974; 1979, manuscript (Box-folder 2/4)
    Articles pertaining to the labor laws, health care, and migrant workers in Florida.
  - Postcards, 1966-1968, 6 black-and-white postcards (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Missouri Conference correspondence, 1970-1981, manuscript (Box-folder 2/6)
    Correspondence between Glen Pearcy and the various church organizations.
  - Note cards, 1994, manuscript (Box-folder 2/7)
    Black-and-white note cards with mailing envelopes of Cesar Chavez speaking at Coachella, California.
  - Salads for Lettuce Boycotters, circa 1970s, manuscript (Box-folder 2/8)
    Informational booklet prepared by Kairos, A United Methodist Church, Kansas City, Missouri and the United Farm Workers.
  - UFW greeting cards, circa 1970s, 8 greeting cards (Box-folder 2/9)
    Greeting cards designed by Susan Pearcy for the Harambee shop which was ran by Southwest Georgia Project.
  - Protestors, circa 1970s, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 2/10)
    Prints of protestors holding signs along with an image of an elderly woman.
  - Magazines, 1973; 1987, 2 magazines (Box-folder 2/11)
    Includes Ramparts and Boycott Grapes, a publication by United Farm Workers (UFW) and other articles about the union.
  - Union Label, Farmworkers, AFL-CIO notebook, 1974, 1 notebook (Box-folder 2/12)
    Includes notes, planning ideas, and sketches.
  - Protest campaigns, sketchbook, 1974, 1 sketchbook (Box-folder 2/13)
    Includes a sketchbook for the Boycott Grapes and Lettuce campaign along with the final drawing of Nixon.
  - Xeroxed drawings and prints for El Macriado, 1972-1973, manuscript materials (Box-folder 2/14)
    Xeroxes of Susan Pearcy's drawings and prints for the El Macriado.
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973, manuscript materials (Box-folder 2/15)
    Letters to Glen and Susan providing feedback on a sermon. Also includes correspondence about the Pearcys' joining the staff at the El Macriado and the history of the United Farm Workers.
  - Celebrating the Past Building for the Future and the National Farm Workers Health Group, 1971-2012, manuscript materials (Box-folder 2/16)
    Pamphlets for the First Constitutional Convention of UFW.
  - Loose drawings, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR118-125; drawings and sketches (Box-folder 2/17)
    A mixture of ink and pencil drawings along with some sketches that can also represent images from the SWGP and UFW organizations.
  - Loose drawing, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR117; 1 linocut on rice paper (Box-folder 6/1)
  - UFW, Fighting for Our Lives, 1973, 1975-undated, 1 newspaper (Box-folder 2/18)
    Includes invitations to the premiere, along with newsletters and newspaper. A copy of The San Francisco Examiner, March 30, 1976, Home Edition was removed from the folder.
  - Huelga, 1970s, 1 poster (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Sketchbook, undated, 2 11 x 14 in. sketchbook (Box-folder 6/4)
    Include images depicting farmworkers. AFC 2014/028: GR51-GR99 also has additional images pertaining to farmwork and the farmers.
  - Sketchbook, undated, 1 14 x 17 in. sketchbook (Box-folder 6/6)
    See above.
  - Long Day, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR51; 1 18 x 12 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Red, black, and white image printed, 2014.
  - Quilt-makers, 1969, AFC 2014/028: GR52; 1 16 x 12 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Black-and-white image on rice paper, printed 2014, (8/25).
  - Cotton picker, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR53; 1 12 x 18 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Black-and-white image printed, 2014, (6/25).
  - Braceros, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR54; 1 17 3/4 x 11 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Boycott lettuce, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR55; 1 9 x 10 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Original prints on newsprint by Susan Pearcy. The drawing depicts a red flag with an eagle symbol.
  - Si Se Puede, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR56; 1 7 1/3 x 11 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Image on rice paper.
  - Farm worker in the field, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR57; 1 9 1/2 x 8 3/4 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Farm worker, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR58; 1 11 x 13 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    A portrait of a worker.
  - Farm worker in the field, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR59; 1 9 x 8 3/4 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Boycott lettuce, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR60; 1 8 1/2 x 11 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Original prints on newsprint by Susan Pearcy. Image of a red flag with eagle symbol inside.
  - Farmworkers in the field (stoop labor), undated, AFC 2014/028: GR61; 1 9 x 14 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Farm worker in the field, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR62; 1 9 1/2 x 9 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Si se puede, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR63; 1 8 3/4 x 11 1/2 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Image, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR64; 1 7 x 5 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Si Se Puede, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR65; 1 7 1/2 x 9 1/3 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
    Image printed on rice paper.
  - Farmworkers in the field (stoop labor), undated, AFC 2014/028: GR66; 1 14 x 9 in. linocut print (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Huelgo, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR67; 1 12 x 18 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/7)
    1 of 3 original drawings of the same series by Susan Pearcy for the El Macriado, 1972-74.
  - Ballot, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR68; 1 12 x 18 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/7)
    2 of 3 original drawings of the same series by Susan Pearcy for the El Macriado, 1972-1974 drawing of a man voting.
  - Men voting, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR69; 1 12 x 18 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/7)
    3 of 3 of original drawings of the same series by Susan Pearcy for the El Macriado, 1972-1974.
  - Paz, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR70; 1 4 1/2 x 5 1/2 in. color drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Paz, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR100; 1 4 1/2 x 5 1/2 in. black-and-white drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Nixon drinks ripple, boycott Gallo wines, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR71; 1 8 1/2 x 11 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    Pencil drawing of Nixon holding a glass of wine.
  - Skull, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR72; 1 12 1/2 x 9 1/2 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    Ink drawing of a skull.
  - Boycott lettuce, non-union, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR73; 1 7 x 5 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    Image of a logo.
  - Boycott grapes, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR74; 1 7 x 5 1/3 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    Ink drawing of a design with grapes in a square sketch on piece of paper
  - Boycott grapes, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR75; 1 11 x 8 1/2 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    A drawing of a bunch of grapes which differs from the design in the preceding folder.
  - Boycott lettuce, non-violence, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR76; 1 8 1/2 x 11 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    Male and female holding a sign.
  - Police, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR77; 1 9 1/2 x 12 1/2 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    A drawing of a police arresting a man. Other protestors and police cars are in the background.
  - Food Stamp office, undated, AFC 2014/028: GR78; 1 12 x 15 1/3 in. drawing (Box-folder 6/8)
    A pencil drawing of man in a room with a box marked free turkey in Food Stamp office.
  - California fields, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR79; 1 4 x 6 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (11/20).
  - Day's End, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR80; 1 7 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (7/50).
  - Ayuno de Amor, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR81; 1 9 x 6 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (8/50).
  - Braceros, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR82; 1 6 x 12 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972/1973 printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (1/50).
  - Stoop Labor, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR83; 1 6.5 x 6.5 in. woodcut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (3/50).
  - Farm Worker, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR84; 1 6 x 4 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (6/25).
  - Orange Picker, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR85; 1 4 x 6 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (8/25).
  - Non-Violence, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR86; 1 5.5 x 4 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (10/50).
  - Farmworkers, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR87; 1 11 7/8 x 6.75 in. woodcut (Box 7)
  - Si Se Puede-Arizona, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR88; 1 3 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (9/50).
  - Si Se Puedo, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR89; 1 3.5 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (10/50).
  - Florida Harvest, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR90; 1 7 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (9/50).
  - Grape Picker, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR91; 1 5 x 7 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2009 on Japanese rice paper, (7/25).
  - Boycott Lettuce, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR92; 1 7 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
  - Hope on the Horizon, 1973, AFC 2014/028: GR93; 1 6.75 x 9.75 in. linocut; The original inventory captures the date for this artwork as 1972. (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1973 and printed in 2014 on Japanese rice paper, (7/50).
  - Boycott Lettuce, 1972, AFC 2014/028: GR94; 1 7 x 5 in. linocut (Box 7)
    Edition created in 1972 and printed in 2009. Picketers carrying signs on Japanese rice paper, (3/50).
  - Standing Woman, 1969, AFC 2014/028: GR95; 1 13 x 13 in. artwork (Box 7)
    A red and black image on rice paper.
  - Standing Woman, 1969, AFC 2014/028: GR96; 1 13 1/2 x 13 in. artwork (Box 7)
    A black-and-white image on rice paper.
  - Standing Woman, 1969, AFC 2014/028: GR97; 1 14 3/4 x 14 in. artwork (Box 7)
  - Farm scene, 1968, AFC 2014/028: GR98; 1 18 x 10 in. artwork (Box 7)
    An image on rice paper.
  - Farm scene, 1968, AFC 2014/028: GR99; 1 17 1/2 x 12 1/2 in. artwork (Box 7)
  - UFW buttons and pins, 19 buttons, pins, and ribbon (Box 8)
    Artifacts displaying the various non-violent and boycott messages of the UFW organization.
  - UFW, El Macriado, 1972, newspaper (Box-folder 10/1)
    Includes 11 newspapers about boycotts and rallies and representation as well as some linocut images.
  - UFW, El Macriado, 1972-1973, newspaper (Box-folder 10/2)
    Includes 9 newspapers compiled about the lettuce strikes and bombing of the office.
  - UFW, El Macriado, 1972-1975, artwork, newspaper (Box-folder 10/3)
    Examples of linocuts that were used in the El Macriado along with newsletters and newspapers.
  - UFW, El Macriado, 1973-1974, newspaper (Box-folder 10/4)
    5 issues of El Macriado.
  - UFW, newspapers, 1973-2014, newspaper (Box-folder 10/5)
    Includes clippings of individuals affiliated with the UFW. Below is a listing of major newspapers that were removed.
    City protests replace UFW picketing, The Bakersfield Californian, August 19, 1973, Vol. 87
    Frank del Olmo, Picketing Halted Farm Union Acts After Two Deaths, Los Angeles Times, August 18, 1973, Daily Edition, Vol XCII
    William Hamilton, Chavez Buried in the Soil of His Struggle, The Washington Post, April 30, 1993
    San Francisco Examiner, March 30, 1976, Home Edition
  - El Teatro Campesino, August 23-September 22, 2013, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR01; 1 color 11 x 17 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    El Teatro Campesino Presents a new play by Luis Valdez, August 23-September 22, 2013. El Teatro Campesino Playhouse, San Juan Bautista, California.
  - We still have a dream, Jobs, Peace, Freedom, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR02; 1 color 14 1/3 x 22 1/2 in. poster (Folder OS01)
  - Farmworkers Week, 1981, Women in Struggle, Mujeres Valiente, 1981, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR03; 1 color 18 x 24 in. poster (Folder OS01)
  - Farmworkers Week, 1981, Women in Struggle, Mujeres Valiente, 1981, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR04; 1 color 18 x 24 in. poster (Folder OS01)
  - When we are really honest with ourselves we must admit that our lives are all that really belong to us..., AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR05; 1 color 14 x 22 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    Poster quotes the words of the leader of the UFW, Cesar Chavez.
  - Vineyard March, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR06; 1 black-and-white 11 x 17 1/2 in. poster (Folder OS01)
  - Farm Worker Week, 1982, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR07; 1 color 17 1/2 x 23 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    Farm worker week, 1982, Women in Struggle, Mujeres Valientes, Local Farm worker week events, look for the UFW, Ask for the UFW label, National Farm Worker Ministry, 1430 W. Olympic Bl., Los Angeles, CA 90015, 213-386-8130.
  - I'm prepared to pay the price for civil disobedience. I was spiritually prepared for the confinement., AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR08; 1 black-and-white 16 1/3 x 22 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    The title of the poster quotes the sentiments shared by the UFW.
  - This Far By Faith, sixty years of migrant history, AFC 2014/028: OS01-GR09; 1 color 17 1/2 x 22 1/2 in. poster (Folder OS01)
    This Far By Faith, sixty years of migrant history, 1920-1980, local farm workers week events, look for the UFW Union Label Union Label Ask for the UFW label, National Farm Worker Ministry 213/386 8130, 1430 W. Olympic BI., Los Angeles, CA 90015.